it's a pretty good time if you wanted to
start a religion now would be a great
time thought must have crossed your mind
if you were to claim since no one's done
it very plausibly for a while but if you
were to claim that that you had yourself
dipped the bucket right down into the
well and brought up a bucket full of the
real thing you could do quite well these
days and my own view is that were quite
lucky that some total charlatan and
hasn't come along with enormous power
already to do that maybe it's less
possible in the modern Information Age
that would have been even in the time of
the founder of Mormonism but let alone
in what used to be called the age of the
prophets but it's always there isn't it
and and and if you have things like
massive societal upheaval or war or
catastrophic events we're all totally
available it's terrifying